Keep running along, watch as we pass by,
as we raise our flag, up high in the sky.
Alright,
here we go now, sailing through the
endless ocean, facing all that comes by.
Let's look for our treasure nobody has
ever got to witness with their own eyes.
All we have to do is keep believing in our
dreams, And let our heart lead the way!
Then once we got all the
others left is to go,
When we face the dark and stormy weather?
Keep the pace, we'll
link our hearts together!
Then I'm sure we'll make it through!
No matter what!
Keep running along, keep running along!
Start raising our flag as we journey on!
Though our chances are close to
none, We won't back down from anyone!
Let's start off the chase!
Toward our own dreams!
While keeping the pace!
With a compass pointing to our goal!
We won't stop till we've gone!
Around the world!
Start me up!
Keep running along!
And we'll never stop!
Till we're at the top!
There's no way that we'll ever quit!
Won't keep heading for tomorrow!
Let's start up the chase!
I see through your eyes!
What we'll have to face!
All the memories we'll say in our hearts!
We'll never let them go!
Brand new world!
Let's start me up!
It's Sanji!
Sanji.
How did you get your body back to normal?
Some big bathtub fell from
the sky and smashed to pieces.
Water went everywhere.
Must have broke the spell.
But more importantly, Nami.
Did you just fall in
love with me all over?
I wish that bathtub had
dropped right on your head.
No, Sop!
Now it's to the point where not even
Sniper or King is in my name, huh?
I'm sorry, Sanji.
I i tried but i couldn't
you're alive that's
what matters everyone has things that they
can do and things that they can't yeah but
both of you take a
look outside huh oh no
it's the Gates of Justice
they're starting to open
Robin.
If those gates open up and
Robin goes through them,
we won't have any way to follow her.
She'll cross waters
infested with sea kings,
and beyond that is either the
Undersea Prison or Navy Headquarters.
Everywhere on the other side of
those gates is beyond our reach.
We'll lose her forever.
But I thought Luffy would
have caught up to her by now.
Dammit!
I can't get through!
Robin's waiting for me!
Just give it up.
You'll never see your friend again.
This is as far as you're going to get.
That isn't going to work on me.
Come on
I said come We're going to the bridge?
Am I gonna make it in time?
I sure hope either this
number three or four key?
Will unlock those damn handcuffs!
But no matter what!
I gotta stop them.
Go this way, go this way.
Come on, Chimney, hurry up.
This tower's in the line of fire, too.
Hold on, Granny.
If I don't show them the way,
everybody's gonna get lost.
Meow, meow.
In hindsight, picking me as your opponent
wasn't the best idea, now was it?
Hey, let us on!
Impossible!
This train is full!
You'll have to find another way!
You bastard!
I thought you were just playing it cool!
You were pretending to be tied up
with your own rope the whole time!
Yeah, I'd say we don't have much time.
What about Big Bro?
What about the Straw Hats?
Those guys are all unstoppable.
There's no need to worry about them.
They'll be fine.
We need to hurry and get
off this island! Yeah!
Ten battleships just departed.
They set sail towards the
island of Eni's lobby.
This is the worst situation I can imagine.
But in every situation, even one as
bad as this, there's always a chance.
Sanji.
Leave this guy's key to me.
Changing my opponent, huh?
Doesn't matter to me.
For now, I'm gonna stay here
and do what you can't do.
You need to do what I can't do.
Huh?
Think carefully.
Read the situation.
As long as we have you, there's
still a chance we can save Robin.
You hear me, Usopp?
As long as you have me, there's
a chance we can save Robin?
And shave.
Get out of here! Right!
Come on, Usopp! Ow! Geez!
I'm still injured!
Don't mess it up!
Staying here and getting
killed will hurt more!
That's a pretty good point!
I thought you were supposed
to be some kind of hunter.
Guess you're nothing but Todd.
Wait now I get it?
Get what we can save? Robin?
As long as I'm here, we can
save her! Damn it! Whoa! Okay?
Do you really have to get
so carried away about it?
Come on!
Let's go! Hey!
Wait up! I've got it! I've got it!
We can save her!
Will you shut up?
That's not exactly something
we want the wolf to?
Looks like I'll get to
kill them after all.
Damn. Direct hit.
Will that piss me off?
Tick finger pistol!
Asien!
Buddy!
Do you think I even felt that?
This punk's got some serious kicks.
That technique you guys use to
make your body strong as iron?
Yeah, it's a really big pain in my ass.
Tip his kick, lone wolf!
Azkoth, Longe, Tendron, Gatshek,
Hazeera, Po, Twiso, Giri, Po!
Oh, shot!
How many times have I got to tell you?
Your kicks do nothing to me!
I'm the only master of the
six powers that can move
around freely while using
the iron-body technique.
You're telling me this like I care.
Is he actually staying down?
Nicely done.
I've been waiting for a worthy
opponent, and I've finally found him.
Now if you don't mind me asking a
favor save robin for me what what
are you talking about Nobody knows
this but robin is this is difficult
for me to say but she's my long lost
little Sister she's what i had no
idea i mean she never said anything
about having an older brother before
I'm not surprised i can't
help her now i'm not strong
enough so please i'm on my
knees begging You you have to
save robin sure i can do
that leave it to me i'll just
pick up this key here and
then I'll be off to save her.
You really think I'd buy that?
My darling Robin is your
long-lost little sister?
Dumbass.
I'll have to kick you
twice as hard for that one.
Hasn't it sunk in yet?
You can fight as hard as you possibly can,
but I am not going to let
you through those doors!
No, you're wrong!
Because no matter how hard you
fight, I'm still gonna get past you!
I doubt that we'll ever agree on this!
So there's no sense in us discussing it!
And I don't have time for talking!
Anyway
Am I finally starting to make
an impression on you, wolf?
Hey! That's my key!
Well, yeah, you did give it to me.
You bastard.
Body Kenpo!
Later!
Get back here!
I'm the one who's supposed to
trick people around here, damn it!
How dare you mock me and steal my gimmick!
Shake!
Party!
Damn, bloody Kimbo!
We so shoot!
Oh, shit!
Damn, Swerve!
Now I'm pissed off!
If you want to get hurt
that bad, I'll oblige you.
Iron body kin-fu, wolf plantain stance!
Wolf hunt, high speed, crack!
Heavy wolf paw! Whoa!
How's that iron-body punch feel?
Probably gonna ache for the rest
of your short, pathetic life.
Moonwalk!
And let's kick!
You must fall!
That was a pretty stupid move you made back
there trying to steal my key and run off
while I'm still alive
I'm a wolf you dolt I
won't stop chasing you
until you're in my jaws
Still hanging in there huh I'm not going
anywhere pal I'm not
about to get killed either
And I'm not gonna forgive you forgive me
Upset with the way we've treated
Robin getting all emotional will only
clutter up your mind During a fight
don't waste all of your precious
time pitying that hopeless fool of a
woman when You should be busy trying
to think of a way to get out of here
alive watch your damn mouth wolf
You don't want to see me mad I
tend to overheat when I'm mad you
aren't going to win this battle
By tossing around threats it's
pretty obvious how badly injured
you are though I'm more than
happy To put you out of your
misery iron body ken po devil wolf
Go ahead and laugh it up.
It's the last chance you'll have.
I don't get the point of this.
You're trying to make me
dizzy from watching you?
Whoa, what happened?
Why's his foot all red like that?
The foot of the devil.
Diablo Jamba.
The heat I generated from all that spinning
will burn my kick straight through you.
It's glowing!
it burns the heat of its destructive
power burns hotter than the flames of hell
I'm burning up!
Even my bones feel like they're melting!
My heart-body won't work!
How the hell can one
kick possibly do that?
Moron!
You don't jump in the air while
you're fighting a six powers master!
God bless, champa!
Premier, action!
Too bad!
What a rookie mistake.
You got in a big hurry to
win and you got sloppy.
So long, sucker.
Moonlight to the finger pistol!
So you knocked one hand away. Big deal.
If your other kick could
have landed in time,
you might have stopped my
finger pistol from hitting you.
Well, I had no choice.
I had to get you close enough to
finish you off with my last kick. Huh?
Diablo Jamba?
Wait!
Ramage!
John!
God may have created food,
but the devil created spices.
If you think that cake was hot,
my heart was burning even hotter.